https://repo.openeuler.org/openEuler-24.03-LTS/everything/aarch64/

What is the command for changing passwords again?

Oh yeah passed

i want each character status panel to be clickable when its the heroaction phase and when it's clicked, I should be able to see another like right click looking panel with the skill options and when i click it should put me in a mode where i can click on any character on the battle field as a target

Theres a relationship with c

When menu is shown and its clicked out side, /
Update menu target selection cuz to support AOE /

Remove the redundancy of apply visual needing width and height when its already specified in the registeredAnimation / (kinda) /

Bruh Character constructor accepts an imageKey, does it clash with register animation?
	no It doesnt, asset manager resolves that identifier /

Add VFX overlay on selected targets easily called in the  /

Add another popup when selecting skills to show skill description /

Turn and game doesn’t end automatically when final blow is from an animation
	Fixed when added onSkillComplete callbacks to call advance turn cycle when skill is done executing
	(the beginnings of callback hell) /

Each level has a fix amount of xp gained when cleared.

Battle controller react to attack feature /

I found a conflict of how the character set image key work and the characterStatusPanel’s setCharacter data  and refreshUI and how it interferes with the newly set animation done on the same panel / fixed with call back hell

It’s a bit confusing but Character<-Hero<-JobClass-skills (and) reactions but Character<-Enemy (has reactions) 
So like different ways of instantiation but Character class has a reaction  list anyway. / NAHH DOESN’T NEED FIXING

Create centralized message board like in the middle of the level “PICK A TARGET” “X casts X on X”, basically an extension of the LogManager, module 

Make another class helper that calculates damages easier based on sam’s damage document, everything should be static. /

Make another animation option that stops or makes the character disappear /

Make a list<list<>> floors then the level schema, enemies, item drops and etc.

Add xp and description /

I noticed the boss is instantiated differently from the enemies, is this on purpose?
I don’t think its a bad thing, I think its necessary for procedural  

Lots of enemies still need to rework some animation logic /
 
I NEED A BACKGROUND ON THIS SHIT /

I NEED A STATUS EFFECT SYSTEM OMG

Should add a battle UI logic to be more specific on types of enemy selection, currently, enemies that are dead cannot be selected during the target and I still want to keep selecting the targetting types that are only valid.
For this we can shift the logic, we can probably instead of having fixed… nvm targeting types in the front end is just better lol.

Items of different rarities have different names higher rarity items have higher base effects and sometimes special effects. 

Refine the UI, ADD UX EFFECTS AND FEEDBACK

EXPAND LOGUI COLORS MAN

Renamed MainView to BattleInterface 
Renamed SkillTarget to TargetType because Items also utilize it

Game loader
	level

I just figured out something, each level has an enemy party with a unique name, how will we procedurally generate those names?
Oooooh I just thought of a solution, we make some predefined parties and for each level we randomly choose a party of each section.

When selecting a skill or item, highlight available targets to use it on!!!!! /

Procedural level generations have drop rate scaling based on the rarity types heheheheheehhe /

STATUS color effects still not working /

Status logs should be moved on the highlight 

Work on the music module

Might make a hero repository /

Moved all setup logic into the gameloader. Abstracted bosses with boss class. Modified all current enemies to support factory generation or something. Added floor generation (only mobs for now). Changed level label. Added xp and loot clear for each level. /

Story board cutscene /

Do the proper refactoring in order to document the OOP design principles properly

Save file details (latest run, gameplay time)

SHA protection to json save file 

Dice and asset manager and etc. are different types of singletons

Explain the roles of each package 

Reuse character selector in “add new character” and add CRUD in character selector V2

Remove redundant imports

Solve issue wherein main menu needs resources that are loaded in game flow but is instantiated before.

Animation does not account for death because of the bug feature thing with the character display, rephrase… /
Animation does not specify death and revive, get JLabel by ID then pause the animation. /

Create modal for items that is received.

Make It so that when onConfirm, clicking outside the selections will cancel the skill

Cured IOC and OCD moved imagekeys to jobclass /

Prolly should seperate the actual battle view then 


IMPROVE THE FUCKIGN UI ITS SOO ASSSASFSIFHASUF

Panel to panel transitions


A TRADER COMES BEFORE YOU!!!, POPS UP TRADE STUFF


Doing the save system rn, needs to clarify how default heroes get instantiate.
Okay so there are party members and there are member benched, when u acquire more members
You need to replace those members

Use the jobFactory in the character selection screen so I don’t have to use character repository


Made the item flyweight factory utilize string mapping for state reasons, modified character level
Scaling logic implementation to be more consistent, made changes to jobs API, added more fields 
And comments for flurger. Added serializable DTO’s for saving game state. Saving now works. /

Your documentation sucks, barely any comments, return type doesn’t show if it can be null

The current battle background didn’t save tho HAHAHAHAHAH

I broke the stat calculator, nah it’s just the rogue. 


Item selector should be more UX friendly,

Character selection panel as anit

Wow really need to update the log colors and lo color implementations

Add baseAtk to the CharacterSelector

Alright, we didn’t account for baseAtk. For most of our shit, my gawd.

Stages for cutscenes and stuff

Refractored a lot of the skill logic, react logic API to an asynchronous callbacks so that attacks can be seen one after another. Got
Rid of the process reaction single pipeline now logics just need to return the actual effect damage instead of -1 and etc.

Warrior disappears after an attack,

Revive isn’t asynchronous / it is now

Should have save file CRUD or just overwrite existing save file

Add a settings page

Lvl 1
Before: 150/150
Mp 100/100 

Lvl 2
Before 150/161
Mp 100/102

Lvl4
151/184

Lvl 6
148/207
108/114

Lvl9
148/242
108/203

When dead: 
Level stays the same
Health 148/150???


Set health with a source parameter looks arbitrary and fishy

Leveling up can now heal and restore the gained hp and mp respectively.
Fixed the health and mp scaling not working when saved, it is because it is not using the proper scaling methods.
Arbitrary values like 4 and 2 hp and mp flat values respectively is embedded into the levelup method instead of
Simply calling the recalculate stat function. Also made the region resources value smaller, might need some more tweaking.
P.S. you can set different scaling values for each job, I made it so. Ex. Wizard’s mp can scale faster than hp. I am saying this
Because right now, we are still using the same arbitrary scaling values that was in level method.

Frozen

Save screen
Settings screen
Character panel in the item can select out	

Before we set the battle controller phase we need to play the cutscene
